going to look at every single carbon
right that's what it asked us to find
the hybridization for each carbon in the
structure so let's start off with just
this one and I can kind of even just
cover this right okay I just want to
look at the bonds or lone pairs in this
case just bonds that are surrounding
that atom that would be four that would
be four exactly so that would then be
sp3 yep oh see I really struggled with
hybridization for some reason okay
and then now let's move on to this
carbon so how many bonds again same same
thing four bonds
and now looking at this one how many
electron groups do we have that would be
three three correct because this only
counts as one so then we know it's SP2
what about the next carbon also three
yeah
so SP2 yes yeah yeah three electron
groups good and then moving on to this
carbon that would be four electrons
great what about that one how many
electron groups do we have that one's
two great yeah
and then the last one's also too that's
a